漫威出品
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     苏小黛
翻译     铁拳章鱼
校对     奶卫联盟
时间轴     大葱
后期     拳拳和马律师的8T
总监     奶卫联盟
人人影视Pro
人人影视官方唯一APP
在线观看，离线缓存，百度云
app.YYeTs.com
官方网站下载 : 人人影视Pro
最新海外影视剧下载
人人影视Pro
人人官方唯一APP
在线观看，离线缓存
几个月前
谢谢你  卡迪尔
Thank you, Kadir.
美味
Excellent.
请告诉您妻子  她的厨艺
Please tell your wife she makes it even better
比在君士坦丁堡时更精进了
than they did in Constantinople.
我想您指的是伊斯坦布尔  女士
I think you mean Istanbul, ma'am.
君士坦丁堡是古称
Constantinople, this is its ancient name.
当然
Of course.
黑空
The Black Sky.
找到了
We have it.
你等了多久
How long have you waited for this?
太久了
Too long.
我们仅剩的资源都用在这上面了
This will use the last of our resources.
你确定值得冒这个险吗
Are you sure it is a risk worth taking?
我再确定不过了
I have never been more sure of anything.
我知道你害怕  但是会过去的
I know you're afraid, but that will pass.
疼痛也会过去的
So will the pain.
没事了
It's all right.
退后
Stand down.
这里就是你的家了
This is your home now.
我们是你的家人
We are your family.
为了见你  我等了好久
I have waited so long to meet you.
放松
Easy.
别紧张  孩子  放松
Easy, my child. Easy.
放松
Easy.
吃吧
Go ahead.
你需要恢复体力
You'll need your strength.
语言能力也会恢复的
Language will come back to you.
还有你的本能
So will your instincts.
至于其他的
But everything else...
只怕本来也没什么保留的价值
I'm afraid it wasn't worth keeping anyway.
你
You...
我是亚历山德拉
My name is Alexandra.
你出生了
You were born.
你活过  又死了
You lived and died.
而你在那边所看到的
And what you saw on the other side...
那黑暗  那无边的虚空
the darkness, the absence of everything...
很可怕  是不是
it's horrifying, isn't it?
我也见识过
I have seen it, too.
不止一次
More than once.
而我这一生所求  就是再也不要经历那一切
And all I want in this life is never to see it again.
不过既然我们相遇了
But now that we've been brought together...
就不必再担心那些了
that's not something we need to worry about.
谁
Who?
我的孩子
My child...
你  就是一切
you... are everything.
你是一切
You are everything.
不管你选择什么
It doesn't matter what you choose.
你可是黑空
You are the Black Sky.
说到底  你自己就是武器
In the end, you are the weapon.
胁差
Wakizashi.
选得好
Good choice.
等到敌人反应过来  已经晚了
They won't know what's coming till it's too late.
她准备好了
She's ready.
拿给她
Bring it to her.
你问了我一个问题
You asked me a question.
答案就在这里
This is the answer.
你的身份就在这里
This is who you are.
捍卫者联盟
第一季  第三集
现      在
她可以见你了
She's ready for you.
你花了一辈子
The war that you've been
打的那场战争  棍叟  已经结束了
fighting your entire life, Stick, it's over.
只要铁拳没死  就没结束
Long as Iron Fist lives, nothing's over.
他在哪
Where is he?
我倒想知道呢
Damned if I know.
我们不再跟你玩刑讯那一套了
We're not doing the torture song and dance.
不再弄了
Not anymore.
可惜
Shame.
我倒有点舍不得了
I grew to like that part.
丹尼·兰德已经失踪好几个月了
Danny Rand has been running around off the grid for months.
他以为他自己就是一支军队
He thinks he's a one-man army.
他这种人很难得
He's a real handful.
我见过更难得的
I've seen better.
可是你剩下的这些时日里
Still, you'll spend the rest of your days
还是整天提心吊胆
looking over your shoulder.
而且据我所知
And from what I hear...
你时日无多啊
those days are numbered.
对嘛
Now...
-这才是我认识的亚历山德拉  -仔细听
- that's the Alexandra I know. - Pay attention.
你交新朋友了
You make a new friend?
错  棍叟  我抢了你朋友
No, Stick. I took one of yours.
-艾丽卡  -你认识的那具肉身已经死了
- Elektra. - The vessel you knew is gone.
只有黑空还活着
Only the Black Sky lives.
听我说  孩子  她满口胡扯
Listen to me, kid. She's full of shit.
-我们得把你救...  -铁拳在哪
- We gotta get you out... - Where is the Iron Fist?
我宁可死  也不会让他加入你
I'll die before I let him join your army.
你以为我想招他做打手吗
You think I want him to fight for me?
他是件武器  你是个怪物  不然呢
He's a weapon. You're a monster. What else?
你给昆仑卖了一辈子命
After a lifetime of serving K'un-Lun...
却还是不知道他到底是什么
you don't even know what he is.
不知道
No.
但我知道我是什么
But I know what I am.
这可是你自找的  艾丽卡
You asked for it... Elektra.
你今晚会死在这里  老头
You'll die here tonight, old man.
-总算死了  -那可不一定
- Finally. - Don't you bet on it.
老混蛋
Son of a bitch.
-你是公设辩护律师  -不是
- Are you a public defender? - Uh, no.
那你来干什么
Then what are you doing here?
一位朋友介绍我来的  他是...
A friend referred me. He works for...
-我猜猜  杰瑞·霍加斯  -对
- Let me guess, Jeri Hogarth. - Right.
我倒没听说她还挺注重弱势群体权益
I didn't know she did diversity hires.
我独立执业  不是她的律所的
Uh, I'm independent. I don't work for her firm.
-那我可不给你钱  -你不必给钱
- Well, I'm not paying you. - You don't have to.
-因为她会给钱吗  -是
- Oh, 'cause she'll foot the bill? - Yeah.
而且我是天主教徒  越难的案子越喜欢接
And I'm a Catholic. I have a soft spot for hopeless causes.
-笑话太冷  抱歉  -没听出来
- That was a bad joke. Sorry. - Barely.
那么琼斯小姐
Uh, Ms. Jones,
我能问下你当私家侦探多久了吗
may I ask how long you've been a PI?
不能
No.
你总是这么粗暴对待帮助你的人吗
Are you always this rude to people trying to help you?
这么着吧  我自己去找律师  谢了
You know what? I'm gonna find my own lawyer, thanks.
好吧  其实你不用找律师
Okay. Uh, well, in reality, you don't need one.
我在外边和负责警探谈了谈
After talking to the lead detective outside,
看来尽管你被牵扯进这么大的麻烦里
it appears that despite the mess you got yourself into,
纽约警局并没有什么能拘留你的证据  所以
the NYPD doesn't actually have anything to hold you on, so...
所以我可以走了
So I can walk?
不过你的公寓和办公室
Though your apartment and office
仍然是在办案件的犯罪现场
are still considered an active crime scene.
你得随时准备接受后续讯问
You'll need to make yourself available for follow-up questions,
-所以在此期间  -我不能出城
- so in the meantime... - Don't leave town.
那一套我懂的
Yeah, I know the drill.
琼斯小姐  我  能不能
Ms. Jones, can... May... Uh...
我也不知道怎么说才好
Look, there's no easy way to say this.
但我看过你的档案  我知道你是谁
I read your file. I know who you are.
你能做什么
What you can do.
我也知道基尔格雷夫的事  所以如果
I know what happened with Kilgrave, so if...
-这跟那些没有任何关系  -好的  那么
- This has nothing to do with that. - Okay, great. Then...
我只是想  正式地问一下
Look, I'm... I'm just saying, legally,
有没有什么  我会保密的
if there's anything, this will stay between us if...
这件案子有没有什么
this was... There's anything not,
不寻常的地方
uh, ordinary about this case.
我说"我懂的"  你哪个字不明白
What part of "I know the drill" did you not understand?
一切正常
Nothing happened.
说完了
I'm good.
很好  那你可以走了
Great. Then I guess you're free to go.
马尔科姆  是  我刚刚录了口供
Malcolm? Yeah, I just gave my statement.
你还好吗  你到底告诉了他们什么
Are you okay? What exactly did you tell them?
怎么回事
What happened?
那些孩子们都被一个
The kids are being recruited
道上人称白帽子的人招募了
by some guy known on the streets as White Hat.
我不知道他有什么计划
I don't know what he's up to,
但他们似乎在做一些清理的活计
but they're doing some kind of clean- up work.
-清理什么  -我没看到  不过
- Cleaning up what? - I didn't get a look, but...
出什么事了
What's wrong?
那个小子  科尔
That kid, Cole...
被警察抓住了
cops just picked him up.
可能现在已经进监狱了
He's probably in jail by now.
-我没去救他  克莱尔  -没事的
- I left him behind, Claire. - It's okay.
不  有事
No, it's not.
你没进监狱  就是最好的
You're better off not in prison.
我更喜欢你在这里
I like you here.
怎么了
What happened?
被人打了
I got clocked.
-白帽子吗  -不是  我不知道他是谁
- By White Hat? - No. I don't know who he was.
但他那一拳就像铁锤一样
But when he hit me, it felt like a sledgehammer.
他那个  拳头
He had this... this hand.
好像发光了
I think it glowed.
怎么个发光法
Glowed how?
我不知道  就是个白人瘦小子
I don't know. Just some skinny white kid.
他的拳头
He had this fist and...
-你打给谁  -有个人你需要见见
- Who you calling? - There's someone that you need to meet.
-他打的我  -你先打的
- He punched me. - You punched first.
不是吧
Seriously?
-我怎么伤不到他  -你拳头又是怎么回事
- How come he can't be hurt? - What's the deal with that fist?
-我应得的  -什么
- I earned it. - You what?
他赢来的
He earned it.
有一个叫做昆仑的秘境  而且...
There's this mystical place called K'un-Lun, and it's...
我可以自己说
I can answer myself.
有一个叫做昆仑的秘境
There's a mystical place called K'un-Lun.
逗我玩呢吧  拜托
Oh, this is a joke. Come on.
我父母坠机死了
My parents died in a plane crash.
我被一群僧侣收养了
I was adopted by a group of monks.
我在那里学会了召唤我的气
There, I learned how to summon my chi.
我就是不朽铁拳
I'm the Immortal Iron Fist.
你就是为了这个去的中国
Is this why you went to China?
你那天晚上看到的  还有这个白帽子
Whatever it is that you saw last night, this White Hat guy...
可能就跟丹尼和科琳
could be connected to the people
一直在对抗的人有联系
Danny and Colleen have been fighting.
就是这群人袭击了
The same people who attacked
克莱尔工作的医院
the hospital that Claire was working at.
你是说你知道这个白帽子是谁
You're saying you know who this White Hat guy is?
不知道  但我知道他是手和会的人
No. But I think he's with the Hand.
那是一个犯罪团伙
It's a criminal organization.
不知道历史有多久
No telling how old they are.
也不知道影响力有多大  他们无所不在
Nor how much influence they have. They are everywhere.
力量无远弗届
In everything.
他们的全部力量
All of their power
都来源于他们复活死人的能力
stems from their ability to bring back the dead.
好吧  我不知道我能接受多少
Okay, I don't know how much of this I can take.
-太疯狂了  -刀枪不入也差不多
- This sounds insane. - And so does being bulletproof.
你们两个都相信我  所以拜托你们听我说
The two of you trust me, so please listen when I say...
你们是一边的
you're on the same side.
我们先不打扰了  你们俩好好谈谈
Now, we're gonna leave you two alone, and you're gonna talk.
只动口
Talk.
几个月前  我们计划要去度假
Couple months ago, we were planning a vacation.
他想去躲一躲
He wanted to get away.
根本说不通
Doesn't make sense.
我来找你
I came to you...
是想查清真相  结果
for answers. And now...
纽约警局已经接手调查了  不过
Well, the NYPD is on the case, but...
我还是想私下继续调查
...between us, I would like to keep investigating.
-你是说不和警方合作吗  -是
- You mean without the police? - Yeah.
我不知道我还能付你多少钱
I don't know how much I can afford.
先别管那些了
Don't worry about that right now.
好的
Okay. Okay.
还有没有什么你没告诉我的事
Now, is there anything you haven't told me?
黄赌毒之类的  或者参与了什么
Drugs? You know, gambling, weird fetish shit? Was there any world
-地下组织之类的  -都没有
- that he was a part of? - No. No.
怎么了  你查到了什么
Why? What did you see?
我觉得有人盯上他了
I think someone was targeting him.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我还不确定
I'm not sure.
这听起来不像是约翰会做的事
None of this sounds like John.
他不是这种人
He wasn't this kind of person.
而且我知道的都告诉你了
And there's nothing I'm not telling you.
别的我也不知道了
There's nothing I don't know.
他就爱两件事  他的家人和工作
He loved two things. He loved us and his job.
就这些  这就是他全部的生活了
And that's it. That was his whole life.
我很快回来
I'll be right back.
-亲爱的你还好吗  -妈  我挺好
- Hi, sweetie. How are you? - Hi, Mom. I'm okay.
很快就会查清楚了
I'm sure we'll find out soon.
你不如先去休息吧  晚饭我来做
Why don't we lay you down, and you can let me fix you supper.
你家的事我很遗憾
I'm sorry about what happened.
告诉你妈妈我走了
tell your mom I let myself out.
喂
Hello?
您好  这是给安娜·艾舍尔的回电
Hi, I'm returning a call from Ms. Anna Asher.
-什么  -这里是邓肯-多特设计事务所
- What? - This is Duncan and Dotter Design.
对对  我就是  抱歉
Oh, right, this is her. Sorry.
-您今天下午有时间吗  -有的
- Um, can you come in this afternoon? - Sure.
第十大道221号  305房间
211 10th Avenue, suite 305.
-305  好  -谢谢您  艾瑟尔小姐
- 305. Got it. - Thank you, Ms. Asher.
你挺能打
You can fight.
你挺能挨
You can take a punch.
克莱尔说他们拿你做实验
Claire said they did experiments on you.
说来话长
Long story.
什么实验
What kind?
自愿的吗
Was it voluntary?
是他们强迫我的
They made me this way.
你知道这个就够了
That's all you need to know.
你说的"气"是指什么
What did you mean, "Chi"?
是一种能量
It's a... It's an energy force.
-好吧  -我们人人都有
- Okay. - We all have it.
可没你那样的
Not like that.
我受训多年
I trained for years.
有一个测试
There was a test.
还有一条龙
There was a dragon.
不是吧
No, there wasn't.
比我想的要和谐多了
It's going better than I thought it would.
我知道听起来扯  但的确是真的
I know how it sounds, but it's true.
你得承认  一般人都会觉得龙的事就是胡扯
You gotta admit, that dragon shit, from the outside...
确实听着挺疯狂的
does sound pretty crazy.
你真的觉得他们会互相帮助吗
You really think they can help each other out?
我不知道
I don't know.
只要他们过了互相较劲的劲头
Once they're done with the pissing contest...
谁知道呢
...who knows?
克莱尔说你是个好人
Claire says you're a good guy.
我在努力
I'm trying.
她说你为哈莱姆做了许多好事
She says you've done a lot for Harlem.
我只是  只是帮帮忙而已
Yeah, I just... just wanna help.
我也是
Me, too.
所以我才去了那间仓库
That's what led me to that warehouse.
你管那叫帮助人
You call that helping?
你都快把那孩子打死了
You were gonna beat that kid within an inch of his life.
拜托  我才没有想杀他
Come on. I wasn't gonna kill him.
看起来挺像杀人的
It sure looked like it.
手和会非常危险
The Hand is dangerous.
他们谋杀了我父母
They murdered my parents.
还入侵了这座我誓言保护的城市
Invaded the city I was sworn to protect.
那小子跟那帮人没有任何关系
That kid's got nothing to do with all that.
当然有关系  他为他们做事
Of course he does. He works for them.
-他需要工作  -这不是理由
- He needed a job. - That's not an excuse.
你从来没有为了保护别人去打人吗
You never fought someone to protect someone else?
-当然打过  -那这件事有什么区别
- Of course I have. - Okay, so what's the difference?
区别就是我和他们住在同一个街区
The difference is I live on their block.
区别就是我不像某个富家子
The difference is I'm not some billionaire white boy
自以为自己在维护正义
who takes justice into his own hands
只知道把黑人小子往墙上怼
and slams a black kid against the wall
就为了报私仇
because of his personal vendetta.
过来的路上克莱尔把你的事告诉我了
Claire told me about you on the way over here.
除了那些玄乎的东西  其他的都说了
Not all the mystical parts, but everything else.
钱
The money?
不能因为钱而给我定性
That doesn't define me.
也许不能  但那小子
Maybe not, but that kid is
今晚要在牢里度过  而你不会
sitting in a jail cell tonight and you're not.
-你也一样  -只是这次而已
- Neither are you. - Not this time.
可我已经领教过了不公
But I've seen my share of injustice.
戴白帽子那人  他只是个开始
The guy in the white hat, he's just the beginning.
你没考虑到大局
You're not thinking about the bigger picture.
而你除了你自己  什么也没考虑
You're not thinking about anything but yourself.
你对我根本一无所知
Hey! You know nothing about me.
我知道的够多了
I know enough.
我能认出养尊处优的人
And I know privilege when I see it.
你也许觉得你的力量是自己努力得来的
You may think you earned your strength,
可你其实从出生起就有特权了
but you had power the day you were born.
在龙之前  在气之前
Before the dragons. Before the chi.
你有能够不伤害任何人
You have the ability to change the world
就改变世界的能力
without getting anybody hurt.
这些人用那种方式阻止不了
These people won't be stopped that way.
所以你就要把底层的人也卷入战争之中吗
You're taking the war to the ones at the bottom, is that it?
如果我是你
If I were in your shoes,
我会仔细考虑是否要把那种能力
I'd think twice about using that thing on people
用在那些想要养家糊口的人身上
who are trying to feed their families.
这事没戏  很明显
This isn't gonna work out, it's obvious.
祝好运  哥们
Good luck, man.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我知道你在里面不好过
I know you're having a rough time in here.
是啊
Yeah.
米丝蒂说24小时内就会提审你
Misty says you'll be arraigned within 24 hours...
但我们会想到办法的
but we can figure this out.
有人找你谈过协议吗
Has anyone approached you about making a deal?
我认识一个律师
I know a lawyer.
不会有协议的  那里有那么多死尸
There ain't no deal. There were dead bodies in there.
看起来像是你只是一个打下手的
Looks like you were doing grunt work.
你只是在帮忙清理
Like you were helping to clean up.
-无所谓了  -当然有所谓
- Look, it doesn't matter. - Of course it does.
你不能为自己没做过的事背黑锅
You don't take the blame for something that's not yours.
-不管是谁雇了你  -天  你醒醒好吗
- Whoever hired you-- - Man, would you wake up?
他们在监视着一切
They're watching everything.
到处都有他们的耳目
They got eyes and ears all over.
你跟我谈得越久  情况就越糟
And the longer you talk to me, the worse it looks.
对我们双方都是
For the both of us.
-戴白帽的人是谁  -天  你别管了行吗
- Who's the guy in the white hat? - Man, would you stay away?
他非常危险
He is next-level dangerous.
我也是
So am I.
是手和会干的吗
Is this the Hand?
你想帮我是吗
You wanna help me?
我妈住在埃奇库姆大道555号
My mom, she lives at 555 Edgecombe.
给她带几张彩票
Take her some lotto tickets.
告诉她是我送的
Tell her they're from me.
科尔  告诉我你知道什么
Cole, just tell me what you know.
她最喜欢刮刮乐  明白吗  照做就行
Scratch-off. Those are her favorite, all right? Just do it.
告诉她是我送的
Tell her that they're from me.
告诉她我很想她
Tell her that I'm thinking about her.
-你可以相信我  -我信
- You can trust me. - I do.
告诉她我很抱歉
Tell her I'm sorry.
看起来大个子让你印象深刻啊
Looks like that big guy made quite an impression, huh?
幸好你俩没互殴起来
I am glad that you two didn't end up in a fist fight.
我怕这地方撑不住
'Cause I'm not sure that this place would survive it.
如果他是对的呢
What if he's right?
对什么
About what?
铁拳是赢得战争的一种方式
The Fist is one way to win this war,
但我确实还有别的法子
but I do have others.
这个嘛  你已经试过了
Yeah... and you've tried 'em.
他们是手和会  没法用钱买通
They're the Hand, you can't just buy 'em.
我不是指用钱
I'm not talking about money.
我有人脉  有路子
I have connections, access.
他根本不懂我们在对抗什么
He doesn't understand what we're really up against.
他不明白他们有多危险
He doesn't get how dangerous they are.
我知道  可是
I know, but...
我明明有能力直接通往顶端
why am I fighting street-level operatives
为什么还要跟街头小弟周旋呢
when I have the power to go right to the top?
丹尼  因为你
Because, Danny, you...
你不是生意人
You're not a businessman.
我知道
I know.
可我父亲是
But my father was.
我知道  可你是个斗士
I know, but you are a fighter.
你是战士
A warrior.
那才是你会的  那才是你心里的东西
That's what you know. That's... that's what's in your heart.
而一个好的战士会利用一切能用的工具
And a good warrior uses every tool at his disposal.
我拥有一家大公司51%的股份
I own 51% of a major corporation.
我得试试另一种方法
I've got to try this another way.
你好  我是丹尼·兰德
Hello? This is Danny Rand.
欢迎回来  兰德先生
Welcome back, Mr. Rand.
米查姆先生提过你在国外有生意要照应
Mr. Meachum mentioned you had business to take care of abroad.
是的  所以我才来了  沃德呢
Uh, yeah. That's what brings me here. Where is Ward?
他一个人去出差了
On a business trip himself.
也许我们可以安排在下个月
Perhaps we could schedule something for next month?
我没那个时间
I, uh, don't have time for that.
很不幸  他最快也得下个月才有空了
Well, unfortunately, that's the earliest he'll be available.
有个组织去年开始跟我们做生意
There was an organization that did business with us last year.
-我们有很多生意  -他们自称手和会
- We did lots of business. - Yeah, they call themselves the Hand.
要帮忙拼写吗
You need help spelling that?
听着  不管你听说了什么  都是真的
Look, whatever you heard, it's true.
我知道你很害怕  可你不帮忙我们就无法离开
I know you're scared, but we can't leave until you help us.
-怎么帮忙  -我们追踪到了他们
- Help you how? - We tailed 'em.
我们跟踪他们到了圣保罗  柏林  莫斯科
We tracked 'em to São Paulo. Berlin. Moscow.
他们在全球都建立了空壳公司
They set up shell companies, worldwide.
我们觉得他们现在在纽约有所动作
We think they're doing something here in New York.
我们需要你帮我们查清具体情况
We need you to help us find it.
圣保罗  柏林  莫斯科
São Paulo, Berlin and Moscow?
还有别的地方吗
Anywhere else?
-巴黎  迈阿密  -柬埔寨首都金边
- Uh, Paris, Miami... - Phnom Penh, Cambodia.
我在交叉参照这些城市的短期控股公司
I'm cross-referencing short-term holdings through those cities.
重叠部分有两百处
Two hundred exist in the overlap.
其中三处去年关停了
Three of them shut down last year.
什么意思
What does that mean?
没什么  只是三处都是同一天关停的
Not much, except that they were shut down on the same day.
在关门之前
Before they closed, they all
他们都存款到了在纽约的同一个地方
made deposits into one place here in New York.
我只需要名字
I just need a name.
中城圈金融公司
Midland Circle Financial.
我记得这名字
I remember that name.
沃德给过我们一个要终止合作的公司名单
Ward gave us a list of places to cease doing business with.
一定是手和会
It must be the Hand.
我去公司名录里给你们找地址
I'll get you the address from the directory.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们今晚出击  几小时后
We hit tonight. After hours.
不
No.
还有别的方法袭击他们
There's another way to attack.
我得自己去做
And I gotta do this alone.
很美吧
Gorgeous, isn't it?
就像我们所有的项目一样
Like all of our projects,
是有可持续性的
it was built with sustainability in mind.
-是的  我超级喜欢  -那就好  艾瑟尔女士
- Yeah, I am super into that. - I'm glad, Ms. Asher.
现在  不如你跟我说说
Now, why don't you tell me
你的具体期望吧  关于你公司的...
what you envisioned for your company's--
公共工作空间
Communal workspace.
我们需要个果汁吧
Um, I mean, we're gonna need a juice bar.
-当然  -还有站立式办公桌
- Of course. - Uh, standing desks.
你知道那种健身弹力球吧
You know those bouncy balls
就是有人会坐上去  有人觉得烦那种
that people sit on that some people find annoying?
我觉得要现代化  高端点  但也要简洁
I think it should be modern and high-tech, but also so simple.
一个实用的乌托邦
A pragmatic utopia.
没错  天  我能引用这形容吗
Yes. Oh, my God. Can I quote that?
不用回答了  我就要引用
Don't answer. I'm gonna quote that.
这里有栋我去年在市中心帮忙设计的楼
Here is a property I worked on last year in Midtown.
有更近期的吗
Is there anything more recent?
-什么  -有今年的吗
- I'm sorry? - Anything from this year?
没有我做完的
Not that I've done.
那你公司其他的设计师呢
How about any other architect in your firm?
因为这对我们的公司很重要
Just because it's really important for our brand
我们不仅要走在时代前沿
that we're not only on the cutting edge,
我们就是前沿
but we are the cutting edge.
明白  不过
Yes, but...
你能保守秘密吗
can you keep a secret?
我是非常谨慎的人
I am the face of discretion.
我可以给你看看我们最近的作品
I can show you our most recent work.
一栋位于地狱厨房的建筑
A building in Hell's Kitchen,
是我的同事约翰·雷蒙德设计的
designed by my colleague John Raymond.
中城圈
Midland Circle.
那位设计师在吗
And is that architect on the premises?
我想跟他聊聊
I would love to speak with him.
他不在  这会不在
No, he's... not. Not at the moment.
那客户是谁呢
And who were the clients?
这是机密信息  相信你能理解
That's privileged information. I'm sure you understand.
不过我还有其他建筑
but I do have another structure
你可能会感兴趣
that you might be interested in.
有一栋我们去年在苏豪区推出的大楼
One that we unveiled in Soho last winter.
-请等我一下好吗  -好的
- If you just give me a minute? - Great.
我们那晚见过面
We met the other night.
我们不是偶然遇见  孩子
Oh, we didn't meet, son.
是上帝派你来的
God himself sent you.
你不用瞒着我任何事
You don't have to hide anything from me.
我知道科尔在哪
I know where Cole is.
他在步他哥哥的后尘
He's following in his brother's footsteps.
你知道他们惹了什么麻烦吗
You know what kind of trouble they were into?
不知道
No.
但我听说有尸体
But I hear there are bodies.
听着不像我儿子会做的事  但我以前也错看过他
Don't sound like my son, but I've been wrong before.
说实话  我控制不住  觉得很羞耻
I can't help but feel some shame, to be honest.
但我什么也做不了
But ain't nothing I can do now.
除了祈祷
Except to pray.
我相信祷告的力量
I believe in the power of prayer.
我父亲验证过
My father made sure of it.
但也许还不太晚
But it might not be too late.
科尔之前在为一些坏人工作
Cole was working for some bad people.
我要阻止他们
I'm going to stop 'em.
愿上帝保佑  并一直让你为他行事
May the Lord bless and keep you for doing his work.
我只是在做必要之事
Only doing what's needed.
你跟我儿子正相反
You know, you're the opposite from my son.
他无法承认自己做错了事
He can't admit when he's done something wrong.
而你却无法承认自己做对了事
You can't admit when you done something right.
科尔让我给你带了这些
Uh, Cole wanted me to bring these to you.
是彩票
They're lotto tickets.
他说希望你知道他很想你
He said he wanted you to know he was thinking about you.
那孩子还是有善良的一面的
There is goodness in that boy.
知道吗  他从八岁起
You know, he'd been bringin' me these
就一直给我这些东西
since he was eight years old?
一开始我不知道他从哪来的钱
At first, I didn't know how he was paying for them.
然后我意识到他是用了自己的午饭钱
And then I realized he was using his lunch money.
他说  保持梦想着很值得
He said it was worth it... to keep the dream alive.
来点饼干怎么样  巧克力片
How 'bout some cookies? Chocolate chip.
他跟你说过我都留着吗
Did he tell you I keep them?
那上面有个盒子  但太高了我够不着
There's a... A box in there, but it's too high up for me.
一直都是科尔在放的
Cole's always the one who does it.
喂
Hello?
是的  我就是
Yes, this is she.
中城圈
出了意外是什么意思
What do you mean, some kind of accident?
他们说事发时他在他的号间里
They say he was in his cell when it happened.
我的宝贝  我的宝贝
My... my baby. My baby...
天啊  我的宝贝
Oh, God, my baby!
天  我的宝贝
我的孩子啊
Oh, my babies!
我的孩子们都走了
All my... All my babies is gone!
All my babies is gone!
铁拳在哪
Where's the Fist?
-请报上名字  -兰德集团的丹尼·兰德
- Name, please. -Daniel Rand, of Rand Enterprises.
-您找哪位  -中城圈金融的老总
- Here to see? - The CEOs of Midland Circle Financial.
-您有预约吗  -没有
- Are they expecting you? - Not like this.
这边请
Right this way.
我叫丹尼·兰德
My name is Danny Rand.
去年你们通过我家的公司
Last year, you illegally transferred
非法转移了243万美元的资产
$243 million worth of assets through my family's company.
你们觉得能逍遥法外
And you thought you got away with it.
可我知道你们是谁
But I know who you are.
你们杀了我的双亲  袭击了我家
You killed my parents, attacked my home.
你们是手和会  而我会确保
You're the Hand. And I'm gonna make sure...
兰德先生
Mr. Rand.
我很欣赏你的坦率和热情
I appreciate your candor. And your passion.
我得承认  鉴于我听说到的您的事
And I must say, considering what I've heard about you,
您比我预想中得体得多
you seem much more disciplined than I anticipated.
-你是哪位  -我是负责人
- And who are you? -I'm in charge.
不过  请继续
But, please, go on.
你刚说到你要怎么做
You were telling us what you were going to do.
-默多克  -我们得马上离开
- Murdock! - We need to leave now.
你再敢那样抓我
If you grab me like that again,
我会狠狠揍你  到时候你就知道了
I'll punch you so hard, you'll see.
-我以前来过这里  -你为什么要跟踪我
- I've been here before. - Why are you following me?
-你非常危险  -你算哪门子律师啊
- And you're in serious danger. - What kind of lawyer are you?
你接的这个案子
This case you took,
正将你引向非常凶险的境地
it's leading you toward something truly sinister.
好吧  你是我见过的废话最多的律师
Okay, you are the most full of shit lawyer I've ever met,
我们就别继续感激那重要的声明了吧
and I think we should stop appreciate the magnitude of that statement.
我们去别的地方说
Let's talk about this somewhere else.
我们还是永远别说了
Let's talk about it never.
除非你告诉我怎么做到眼盲了还能那样行动的
Unless you wanna tell me how a blind man moves the way you do.
-什么  -我拍了照片  混蛋
- Excuse me? - I have pictures, asshole.
兰德集团已经在收集证据来扳倒你们
Rand Enterprises has put together a case to take you down.
敲诈勒索  贩毒  贩卖人口
Extortion, narcotics, human trafficking...
我们将曝光的事还远不止如此
There's no end to what we'll uncover.
所以呢
And?
所以你们无法再躲藏了
And you can't hide anymore.
我们看起来像在躲藏吗
Does it look like we're hiding?
躲在中城圈金融背后
Behind Midland Circle Financial.
躲在空壳公司背后
Behind corporate shells,
躲在那些不知道自己
or street-level criminals
在为谁工作的街头罪犯身后  是的
who don't know who they're working for. Yes.
这就是你们做的事
It's what you do.
但我是来曝光你们的
But I'm here to expose you.
我是永生的铁拳  昆仑的武器
I am the Immortal Iron Fist, weapon of K'un-Lun.
-我要履行我的使命  -昆仑
- And I'm fulfilling my destiny. -K'un-Lun.
那里现在可好
How is it these days?
你们会失去一切  就像之前的我一样
You're gonna lose everything. Just like I did.
你没失去任何东西  兰德先生
You haven't lost everything, Mr. Rand.
目前还没
Not yet.
-你干什么  -有人开枪
- What are you doing? - Gunshot.
-在哪  -顶层公寓
- Where? - In the penthouse.
-你怎么知道的  -我就是知道
- How do you know that? - I just do.
这正是我在试图避免的  借我用用
This is exactly what I was trying to avoid. I need that.
我跟以前的铁拳们有过交集
I've crossed paths with Iron Fists before,
但这次不同  因为这次
but this is different, because this time...
我不会杀你
I won't kill you.
用她作掩护根本没有用
No use using her for protection.
他们为了抓到你会直接撕了她
They will rip right through her to get to you.
-你来了  -我来了
- You? - Me.
现在打人就没问题了吗
So punching's okay now?
具体问题具体分析
It's complicated.
你看着像个混蛋
You look like an asshole.
这围巾可是你的
It's your scarf.
-杰西卡  -卢克
- Jessica? - Luke.
-你还好吗  -说来话长
- How you been? - Long story.
我们得离开这里
We have to get out of here.
-他是谁  -说来话更长  他又是谁
- Who's he? - Longer story. Who's he?
等等  还有人来
Wait. There's someone else coming.
不太一样
Something else.
你知道该怎么做
You know what to do.
-怎么回事  -该死
- What is it? - Oh, shit.
-她是谁  -坏消息  我们得走了
- Who's that? - Bad news. We gotta go.
艾丽卡
Elektra?
快走
Come on.
你们是什么人
Who are you people?